A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.33 (A2007) FA492
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2007.007: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1999-2006; AC.2007.007; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3832-R3836.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RESIDENT (Nuthall, Jennifer Jill), 2000-2005 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Ofer, Dalia), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Ojaide, Tanure), 1999-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Osborne, Daphne J.) (CO-RESIDENT: Sen-Mandi, Swati), 1999-2002 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Paine, Jeffery), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Pears, David F.), 1999-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Phongpaichit, Pasuk), 1999-2003 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Pipher, Mary Bray), 2000-2002 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Plumly, Stanley), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Postema, Gerald Jay), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Ricci, Isolina), 2000-2004 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Richardson, James T.), 2000-2002 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Rothman, David J.) (CO-RESIDENT: Rothman, Sheila M.), 2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Rozenblum de Horowitz, Sara), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Sagradini, Mario), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Sandy, Stephen), 2000-2006 (Box R3835)
      Biographical / Historical
    - RESIDENT (Schauffler, Helen Halpin), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Scherpe, Klaus R.), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Schor, Mira), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Schuck, Peter H.), 2000-2003 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Segre, Gino Claudio), 2000-2002 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Seidman, Edward), 2000-2001 (Box R3835)
    - RESIDENT (Shakya, Dilli Devi), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Shapiro, Gary), 2001-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Sikkema, Kathleen J.), 2001-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Silver, Harold), 2000-2003 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Smith, Ethel Morgan), 2001-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Souza, Alfred), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Squier, Susan Merrill), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Stevens, Charles F.), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Stevens, Jane R.), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Stromquist, Nelly P.), 1999-2003 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Taylor, Alan Michael), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Thavinpipatkul, Daranee), 1999-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Thilloy, Pierre), 2001-2006 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Thomasos, Denyse), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Tucker, Nancy B.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Twine, France W.), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Vaid, Krishna B.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Vargas, Antonio P.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Vasavi, Aninhalli R.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Walker, Elizabeth A.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Walker, Vern R.), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Walters, Pamela B.), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Wang, Rui), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Waters, Claire M.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Watson, Stephen F. T.), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Wilkinson, Glenn R.), 2000-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Winet, Jon), 2001-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Wise, Carol) (CO-RESIDENT: Pastor, Manuel), 1999-2002 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Zencey, Eric), 2000-2001 (Box R3836)
    - RESIDENT (Zevit, Ziony), 2000-2003 (Box R3836)
- AC.2007.016: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2005; AC.2007.016; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3839, R3840, R3842, R3843
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2007.016.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2001 WC 083 - YOUTH LAW CENTER - BUILDING BLOCKS FOR YOUTH PROJECT, 1998-2004 (Box R3839)
    - 2001 WC 083 - YOUTH LAW CENTER - BUILDING BLOCKS FOR YOUTH PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1998-2004 (Box R3839)
    - 2001 WC 084 - AMERICAN ASSEMBLY - UNITING AMERICA PROJECT, 2000-2002 (Box R3839)
    - 2001 WC 088 - GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY - WELFARE POLICY IN BRITAIN AND THE UNITED STATES, 2001-2003 (Box R3839)
    - 2001 WC 096 - UPLIFT, INC. - JUBILEE INSTITUTE, 2000-2004 (Box R3839)
    - 2001 WC 099 - COOPERATIVE DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE, INC. - URBAN ENERGY COOPERATIVE DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 2001-2002 (Box R3839)
    - 2001 WC 101 - MATHEMATICA POLICY RESEARCH, INC. - WAGE-PAID TRANSITIONAL WORK PROGRAMS STUDY, 2001-2002 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 102 - ACTIVE CITIZEN FOUNDATION (COSTA RICA) - MEETING ON SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT AND POVERTY IN BORDER COMMUNITIES OF COSTA RICA AND NICARAGUA, 2001-2003 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 104 - NEW AMERICAN SCHOOLS - EDUCATION QUALITY INSTITUTE, 2001-2002 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 112 - INSTITUTE FOR WISCONSIN'S FUTURE - CONFERENCE FOR ORGANIZING THE NATIONAL SCHOOL INVESTMENT NETWORK, 2000-2001 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 114 - HARLEM CONGREGATIONS FOR COMMUNITY IMPROVEMENT - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT IN HARLEM, 2001-2003 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 116 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - SYMPOSIUM ON REGENERATING COMMUNITIES AND IMPROVING HEALTH, 2000 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 118 - NATIONAL INTERFAITH COMMITTEE FOR WORKER JUSTICE - WORKER RIGHTS EDUCATIONAL OUTREACH, 2001-2003 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 119 - GEORGETOWN UNIVERSITY - BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT AMONG SMALL ENTREPRENEURS IN CARIBBEAN-ORIGIN IMMIGRANT COMMUNITIES, 2001-2002 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 121 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - EXPERIENCE OF IMMIGRANT STUDENTS IN NEW YORK CITY PUBLIC SCHOOL SYSTEM, 2001-2005 (Box R3840)
    - 2001 WC 123 - FOOTHOLD TECHNOLOGY, INC. - WEB-BASED CLIENT TRACKING/CASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM, 2001-2002 (Box R3840)
    - 2002 WC 081 - GLOBAL KIDS, INC. - ANNUAL YOUTH CONFERENCE, 2002-2003 (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 083 - CENTER ON BUDGET AND POLICY PRIORITIES - U.S. UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE SYSTEM AND LOW-INCOME TEMPORARY WORKERS, 2002-2003 (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 084 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - UNEMPLOYMENT INSURANCE PROJECT AND LOW-INCOME AND TEMPORARY WORKERS (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 091 - SIERRA HEALTH FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE ON THE ROLE OF COMMUNITY BUILDING IN HEALTH IMPROVEMENT (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 096 - BASIC INCOME EUROPEAN NETWORK (SWITZERLAND) - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON INCOME SECURITY AS A RIGHT, 2002-2005 (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 098 - MUNICIPAL ART SOCIETY OF NEW YORK - POST SEPT. 11TH CREATIVE CITIES CONFERENCE, 2002-2003 (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 101 - TIDES CENTER - LEADERSHIP LEARNING COMMUNITY PROJECT, 2000-2004 (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 139 - COMMUNITY SERVICES PLANNING COUNCIL - NEIGHBORHOOD INDICATOR SYSTEM FOR POOR COMMUNITIES IN SACRAMENTO, CALIFORNIA (Box R3842)
    - 2002 WC 140 - ECONOMIC ROUNDTABLE - NEIGHBORHOOD INDICATOR SYSTEM FOR POOR COMMUNITIES IN LOS ANGELES (Box R3842)
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - BC TEAM: Beckett's Happy Days - an installation, 1993-1995 (Box R3842)
    - BC TEAM: Charting a Global Course for Medical Abortion: New Drugs, Best Practices and Appropriate Policies, 1999-2005 (Box R3842)
    - BC TEAM: Europe and the United States: Comparative Ethnic Literatures, Cultures, and Politics, 1999-2000 (Box R3842)
    - BC TEAM: Gender and Reproductive Training Initiative, 1999-2002 (Box R3842)
    - BC TEAM: Health Maps: A Global Network for Control of Snail?Borne Disease Using Satellite Surveillance and Geographic Information Systems, 1999-2002 (Box R3842)
    - BC TEAM: Resourcing Public Health, 1999-2000 (Box R3842)
    - BC TEAM: Sound of Falling Light, 1999-2001 (Box R3842)
    - CONFERENCE: AIDS Exploration, 2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Altruism and Imperialism: Western Religious and Cultural Missions to the Middle East, 1999-2003 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: American Forms, Global Forums, 1999-2001 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Capturing the Value of Forest Carbon for Sustainable Local Livelihoods, 1999-2001 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Changing Landscape of the Welfare State: Implications for the Future of Social Protection, 1999-2003 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Consensus and Commitment around the Adolescent Component of the Future Global Agenda for Children, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Democracy and Inclusion of the disenfranchised at the local level in politics and schools, 2000-2001 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Developing Efficient and Equitable Health Sector Strategies, 2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Economic Integration and Inequality in the Global Economy, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Environmental Sanitation in the 21st Century, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Feminism and the Shifting Boundaries of Public and Private, 1999-2001 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Gentes, Kings and Kingdoms: The Emergence of States (300-800), 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Honey Bee Socioneurogenetics, 1998-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Leaving No Child Behind in the Third Millennium, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Population and Reproductive Health: The Way Forward for the Rockefeller Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Promoting Socioeconomic Security, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Reflections on Global Institutions for Environment and Development, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Toward a Global Environmental Organization, 1999-2001 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Toward a Global History of Contemporary Women's Movements, 1999-2000 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Transnational Moments of Change in Postwar Europe, 1999-2002 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: Transnationalization of Support for Culture in a Globalizing World, 1999-2001 (Box R3843)
    - CONFERENCE: 2000 Years Transmission of Mathematical Ideas: From Late Babylonian to Early Renaissance Science, 1999-2003 (Box R3843)
- AC.2007.018: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2001-2006; AC,2007.018; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3841.
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2007.018.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2001 WC 124 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - GLOBAL RESTRUCTURING AND CORPORATE CHANGE IN THE TEMPORARY HELP INDUSTRY, 2001-2003 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 127 - JOBS WITH JUSTICE EDUCATION FUND - ECONOMIC JUSTICE EFFORTS IN THE U.S., 2001-2002 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 132 - HEARTLAND ALLIANCE - MEETING, "CORN, COMMERCE AND COMMUNITY", 2001-2003 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 133 - (WORKING COMMUNITIES) - WORKSHOP ON THE GARMENT INDUSTRY IN CENTRAL AND NORTH AMERICA (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 134 - CALIFORNIA TOMORROW - ADDITIVE MOVEMENT IN IMMIGRANT EDUCATION, 1999-2002 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 135 - LEARNING COMMUNITIES NETWORK, INC. - FLINT EVALUATION EXTERNAL ADVISORY GROUP, 2001-2006 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 137 - JUST FOR THE KIDS - QUALITY INDICATORS OF TEACHER LEARNING AND SCHOOL IMPROVEMENT EFFORTS, 2001-2003 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 146 - LOUISIANA CRISIS ASSISTANCE CENTER - CAPITAL DEFENSE REPRESENTATION IN THE SOUTH, 2001-2003 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 147 - PUBLIC ADVOCATES, INC. - CALIFORNIA EDUCATIONAL EQUITY CAMPAIGN, 2001-2002 (Box R3841)
    - 2001 WC 150 - SNITOW-KAUFMAN PRODUCTIONS - DOCUMENTARY, "SECRETS OF SILICON VALLEY", 2001-2002 (Box R3841)
    - 2002 WC 011 - CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY (FRESNO) - NEIGHBORHOOD INDICATOR SYSTEM FOR POOR COMMUNITIES (Box R3841)
    - 2002 WC 070 - BENTON FOUNDATION - EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATIONS FOR IMPROVING WELFARE POLICIES, 2001-2003 (Box R3841)
    - 2002 WC 076 - ASIAN AMERICAN FEDERATION OF NEW YORK - ASSESSMENT OF THE ECONOMIC IMPACT OF SEPT. 11TH ON CHINATOWN (Box R3841)
    - 2002 WC 078 - AMNESTY INTERNATIONAL - CRISIS RESPONSE WORK IN THE WAKE OF SEPT. 11 ATTACK, 2002-2003 (Box R3841)
    - 2002 WC 080 - CITYKIDS FOUNDATION - BRIDGEBUILDER INITIATIVE (Box R3841)
- AC.2007.020: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2005; AC.2007.020; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3844.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2007.020.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9821 - BROWN UNIVERSITY - "LIBRARY OF LATIN AMERICA" BOOK SERIES, 1996-2002 (Box R3844)
    - AH 9956 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - CONFERENCES ON PRIVACY, 1999-2003 (Box R3844)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2007.020.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AS 9811 - ORTIZ CATON, ANDRES - SOIL BIOLOGY RESEARCH ON LEGUME-BASED GREEN MANURE SYSTEMS IN NAYARIT, MEXICO, 1997-2002 (Box R3844)
    - AS 9909 - OCHAI, SULE - NATURAL RESOURCE AND ENVIRONMENT ECONOMICS, 1998-2001 (Box R3844)
    - AS 9920 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME (KENYA) - SOIL BIOLOGY FOR AFRICAN AGRICULTURE AND THE SOIL BIOTA, 1999-2002 (Box R3844)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2007.020.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - EO 9916 - YALE UNIVERSITY - COMMUNITY-BASED WORK OF CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF RACE, INEQUALITY AND POLITICS, 1999-2003 (Box R3844)
    - EO 9925 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - U.S./UK DIALOGUE ON STRENGTHENING BRITAIN'S CAPACITY TO EVALUATE WELFARE-TO-WORK, 1999-2002 (Box R3844)
    - EO 9933 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - CHARTER SCHOOLS IN NEW YORK CITY, 1999-2005 (Box R3844)
    - EO 9942 - UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON - PUBLICATION OF HISPANIC/LATINO CIVIL RIGHTS SERIES, 1999-2002 (Box R3844)
  - Global Engagement (GEE), AC.2007.020.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GEE 9803 - TUFTS UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP/BOOK ON HIGHLY CAPITALIZED ANTI-SOCIAL ACTIVITIES, 1998-2003 (Box R3844)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2007.020.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GP 9904 - LONDON SCHOOL OF ECONOMICS AND POLITIC/IL SCIENCE (ENGLAND) - GLOBAL CIVIL SOCIETY, 1998-2004 (Box R3844)
- AC.2007.024: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1978-1982, 1993-2003; AC.2007.024; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3179A, R3845
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2007.024.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GP 9925 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT (ENGLAND) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1998-2003 (Box R3845)
    - GP 9928 - POPULATION COUNCIL - SEEDS BOOKLETS ON WOMEN'S ROLE IN GLOBAL MARKETPLACE, 1999-2002 (Box R3845)
  - Health Sciences (HS), AC.2007.024.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - HS 9914 - INFANT FEEDING ACTION COALITION (INFACT) (CANADA) - PROTECTING INFANT HEALTH THROUGH THE CODEX ALIMENTARIUS COMMISSION, 1999-2002 (Box R3845)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2007.024.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9920 - ASIA SOCIETY - NETWORK ON SECURITY AND NUCLEAR CHALLENGES IN ASIA, 1999-2002 (Box R3845)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2007.024.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PS 9805 - CHANDRASEKHAR, S. - HISTORY OF BIRTH CONTROL IN INDIA AND FUTURE POLICIES, 1998-2002 (Box R3845)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.024.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 93012 - STRENGTHENING AFRICAN RADIO, 1993 (Box R3845)
    - RF 93018 - STRENGTHENING AFRICAN MUSEUMS, 1992-1993 (Box R3845)
    - RF 93022 #225 - ZHONGSHAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR ZHANG SHANG-HONG, 1997-2000 (Box R3845)
    - RF 93022 #232 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR PHILBERT S. BONILLA, 1999-2003 (Box R3845)
    - RF 93022 #238 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - ORGANIZATION OF LARGE DNA FRAGMENT CLONES IN RICE GENOME, 1993-2002 (Box R3845)
    - RF 93028 #18 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - SAFE MOTHERHOOD PROJECT IN AFRICA, 1995-2003 (Box R3845)
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2007.024.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SI 9815 - PANOS LIMITED (ENGLAND) - COMMUNICATIONS AND SOCIAL CHANGE PROJECT, 1997-2003 (Box R3845)
  - Program and Policy, 900; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PROGRAM AND POLICY, 1978-1982 (Box R3179A)
    - PROGRAM AND POLICY - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL (Pro-65 through Pro-70a), 1978-1982 (Box R3179A)
- AC.2007.030: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1979; AC.2007.030
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120
    - Recording by Chauncey Belknap documenting arrangements made for accepting the legacy of the Villa Serbelloni Bellagio from Ella Walker, Princess Della Torre e Tasso, and purchasing the villa., 1979 June 21 (Item 2007.030.001)
      RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
- AC.2007.034: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2003; AC.2007,034; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3846.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.034.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 93028 #9 - UNIVERSITY OF EDINBURGH (SCOTLAND) - TRAINING AND RESEARCH IN FERTILITY REGULATION, 1993-1998 (Box R3846)
    - RF 93063 #83 - SHANGHAI SECOND MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (CHNA) - MALE FERTILITY EDUCATION, 1997-2000 (Box R3846)
    - RF 94038 #18; RF 94051 #19 - RF 95051 #19 - NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR INDIA - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1993-2003 (Box R3846)
    - RF 95037 #2 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - GRAIN WEEVIL RESISTANCE IN SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1996-2003 (Box R3846)
    - RF 96001 #487 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR TANG KEXUAN, 1996-1999 (Box R3846)
    - RF 96001 #509 - ZHEJIANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - RICE BACTERIAL LEAF BLIGHT, 1989-2002 (Box R3846)
- AC.2007.039: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1996-2004; AC.2007.039; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3847, R3848.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.039.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 96003 #581 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, "LATINO CULTURAL RESEARCH IN A NATIONAL MUSEUM CONTEXT'', 1996-2003 (Box R3847)
    - RF 96003 #582 - NEWBERRY LIBRARY - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (CENTER FOR RENAISSANCE STUDIES), 1996-2002 (Box R3847)
    - RF 96010 #21 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - DISEASE RESISTANCE IN SORGHUM, 1996-2004 (Box R3847)
    - RF 96010 #24 - HARYANA AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR KHAZAN S. BOORA, 1997-2002 (Box R3847)
    - RF 96020 #66 - PROGRAMA LATINOAMERICANO DE CAPACITACION E INVESTIGACION EN REPRODUCCION HUMANA - HUMAN REPRODUCTION, 1988-2002 (Box R3847)
    - RF 96022 #736 - KIPCHUMBA, ALINA - ADIA: BLACK RHINOCEROS IN KENYA, 1997-2004 (Box R3848)
    - RF 96047 - NATURAL RESOURCES MANAGEMENT - MEXICO, 1992-2000 (Box R3848)
    - RF 96047 #112 - AUTONOMOUS UNIVERSITY OF CHAPINGO (MEXICO) - "AGROFORESTRY: RESEARCH TRAINING, AND EXTENSION", 1998-2000 (Box R3848)
    - RF 96048 #56 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GUIDELINES FOR RESEARCH ON REPRODUCTIVE TRACT INFECTIONS/GYNECOLOGICAL MORBIDITY, 1998-2002 (Box R3848)
    - RF 96048 #63 - SWAASTHYA PROJECT (INDIA) - SEXUAL BEHAVIOR AMONG ADOLESCENTS IN TIGRI, 1995-2003 (Box R3848)
- AC.2007.041: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2006; AC.2007.041; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3849, R3850.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.041.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 97001 #523 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1994-2006 (Box R3849)
    - RF 97001 #560 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (ICAR) - TRANSFER OF MALE STERILITY IN INDICA RICE, 1991-2002 (Box R3849)
    - RF 97001 #595 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD (INDIA) - COMMUNITY OF RICE RESEARCHERS IN INDIA, 1997-2004 (Box R3849)
    - RF 97033 #64 - LIVERPOOL SCHOOL OF TROPICAL MEDICINE (ENGLAND) - "A SHORT TEXTBOOK OF PREVENTIVE MEDICINE FOR THE TROPICS", 1998-2005 (Box R3849)
    - RF 97034 #796 - TAMATAMAH, RASHID ADAM - ADIA: PHOSPHORUS FROM RURAL CATCHMENTS FLOWING INTO SPEKE GULF, LAKE VICTORIA, TANZANIA, 1998-2003 (Box R3849)
    - RF 97034 #831 - NATY, ALEXANDER - ACA: DISCOURSE ON ENVIRONMENT AND ECOLOGY AMONG KUNAMA PEOPLE OF WESTERN KENYA, 1996-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #838 - NYANKANGA, RICHARD OMBUI - ADIA: POTATO LATE BLIGHT IN KENYA, 1998-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #843 - KIFLEYESUS, ABBEBE - ACA: ERITREAN RETURNING REFUGEES, 1998-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #850 - MURllTHI, LINUS - ACA: MANAGEMENT STRATEGIES FOR IRISH POTATO BACTERIAL WILT IN KENYA, 1993-2003 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #855 - SHISANYA, CHRIS A. - ACA: RESPONSE OF SMALL-SCALE FARMERS TO POPULATION PRESSURE IN VIHIGA, KENYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #857 - KIIZA, BARNABAS A. - ACA: MICROFINANCE DEVELOPMENT AND POVERTY ALLEVIATION IN UGANDA, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #858 - MPOFU, ELIAS - ACA: SOCIAL ACCEPTANCE OF DISABLED STUDENTS IN ZIMBABWE, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #859 - NZIOKA, CHARLES BONASERA - ACA: ADOLESCENT STREET GIRLS IN NAIROBI, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #860 - MAFELA, LILY - ACA: NON-FORMAL EDUCATION AND GIRLS' RE-INTEGRATION INTO THE EDUCATION SYSTEM IN BOTSWANA, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97034 #863 - MIARON, JACOB OLE - ACA: MAASAI ETHONO-VETERINARY MEDICINAL PLANTS IN KENYA, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97045 #88 - UZIMA FOUNDATION (KENYA) - AIDS AWARENESS AND SEXUAL BEHAVIOR OF YOUTH, 1999-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97052 #588 - UNIVERSITY OF OREGON - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS: ECOLOGICAL CONVERSATIONS PROGRAM (CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF WOMEN IN SOCIETY), 1997-2002 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97052 #589 - UNIVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA (CHAPEL HILL) - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, "CREATING THE TRANSNATIONAL SOUTH" (CENTER FOR INTERNATIONAL STUDIES), 1997-2004 (Box R3850)
    - RF 97052 #592 - UNIVERSITY OF MEMPHIS - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS ON RACE AND GENDER IN MID-SOUTH (CENTER FOR RESEARCH ON WOMEN), 1996-2002 (Box R3850)
- AC.2007.042: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2006; AC.2007.042; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3851, R3852.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2007.042.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 97052 #594 - INSTITUTE OF PERUVIAN STUDIES - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS, "GLOBALIZATION, CULTURAL DIVERSITY AND REDEFENITION OF IDENTITIES IN ANDEAN COUNTRIES", 1997-2003 (Box R3851)
    - RF 97055 - FESTIVAL FUND, 1990-1999 (Box R3851)
    - RF 97057 #67 - ALTERNATE ROOTS - AUDIENCE DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM IN THE SOUTHEAST U.S., 2000-2003 (Box R3851)
    - RF 98001 #614 - UNIVERSITY OF HYDERABAD (INDIA) - DISEASE RESISTANCE IN RICE, 1993-2002 (Box R3851)
    - RF 98001 #618 - ZHEJIANG ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES (CHINA) - EVALUATION OF TRANSGENIC RICE FOR VIRUS RESISTANCE, 1997-2005 (Box R3851)
    - RF 98001 #631 - MAHYCO RESEARCH FOUNDATION (INDIA) - MARKER-ASSISTED SELECTION (MAS) AND RICE, 1997-2002 (Box R3851)
    - RF 98001 #667 - MADURAI KAMARAJ UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF INDICA RICE FOR SHEATH BLIGHT RESISTANCE, 1998-2003 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98001 #683 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR P. BALASUBRAMANIAN, 1998-2003 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98001 #697 - BIOTECHNOLOGY RESEARCH CENTER - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR SU JIN, 1998-2003 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98001 #702 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - INTROGRESSION OF QUANTITATIVE TRAIT LOCI AND NEW RICE CULTIVARS, 1998-2003 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98005 #154 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - NITROGEN FIXATION FACILITY, 1997-2004 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98009 - CAREER DEVELOPMENT FELLOWSHIPS IN THE AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES, 1994-1999 (Box R3852)
    - RF 91060 #18; RF 98011 #39 - HEBEI ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL AND FORESTRY SCIENCES (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR WANG ZHIMIN, 1998-2006 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98013 #194 - RAND CORPORATION - COMMUNICATING POPULATION POLICY RESEARCH, 1996-2003 (Box R3852)
    - RF 98023 #22 - (HEALTH SCIENCES) - BC CONFERENCE: RESOURCING PUBLIC HEALTH IN THE 21ST CENTURY, 1999-2001 (Box R3852)